Finding Aid for the Collection of Television Film Scripts PASC.0074
UCLA Library Special Collections
- SILENCE OF THE HEART, (3/1/1984) (Box > 81)
- SILENCE OF THE HEART, (4/4/1984) (Box >191)
- SILENT RUNNING, (2/1/1971) (Box >198)
  Writers: Trumbull, Douglas; Cimino, Mike
- SILENT VICTORY: THE KITTY O'NEIL STORY, (11/6/1978) (Box >139)
- SILHOUETTE, (5/16/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Wolf, Jay; Buell, Victor
- SILHOUETTE, (5/16/1990) (Box >240)
- SILVER STRAND (THE), (no date) (Box >206)
- SINATRA, PART I, (4/22/1991) (Box >123)
  Writers: Mann, Abby; Mastrosimone, William
- SINATRA, PART II, (7/15/1991) (Box >123)
- SINGLE BARS, SINGLE WOMEN, (5/18/1984) (Box >181)
  Writers: Bortman, Michael
- SINS OF THE FATHER, (10/12/1984) (Box >181)
- SINS OF THE FATHERS, (1/11/1988) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Eszterhas, Joe
- SINS OF THE PAST, (2/12/1984) (Box >169)
  Writers: Brown, Steve; Solomon, David
- SITTER (THE), (1/2/1991) (Box >125)
  Writers: Berger, Rick
- SIX AGAINST THE ROCK, (2/13/1987) (Box > 34)
- SIZZLE, (3/13/1981) (Box > 98)
  Writers: Ware, Clyde; Carr, Richard
- SKETCH ARTIST, (8/6/1991) (Box >216)
  Writers: Angeli, Michael
- SKETCH ARTIST II: HANDS THAT SEE, (6/17/1994) (Box >248)
- SKI LIFT TO DEATH, (11/17/1977) (Box >119)
- SLAB BOYS (THE), (no date) (Box >248)
  Writers: Byrne, John
- SLOW BURN, (10/15/1985) (Box >149)
  Writers: Chapman, Matthew; Lyons, Arthur
- SMALL SACRIFICES, (7/26/1989) (Box > 95)
- SMALL SACRIFICES (PARTS I, II), (2/16/1989) (Box > 74)
  Writers: Eliason, Joyce; Rule, Ann
- SMASHUP ON INTERSTATE FIVE, (4/26/1976) (Box >162)
- SMASHUP ON INTERSTATE FIVE, (4/10/1976) (Box >142)
- SNATCHED, (10/11/1972) (Box >250)
- SNATCHED, (11/10/1972) (Box >118)
- SNOWBEAST, (7/20/1976) (Box >156)
- SOLITARY MAN (THE), (2/1/1979) (Box > 87)
- SOMEONE I TOUCHED, (10/30/1974) (Box >193)
- SOMEONE I TOUCHED, (no date) (Box >251)
- SOMETHING ABOUT AMELIA, (1/14/1983) (Box >195)
- SOMETHING EVIL, (10/15/1971) (Box >252)
- SOMETHING FOR JOEY, (10/7/1976) (Box > 59)
  Writers: McNeely, J.
- SOMETHING IN COMMON, (no date) (Box > 27)
- SOMETHING TO LIVE FOR, (10/17/1991) (Box >214)
  Writers: LeVine, Deborah Joy
- SOMETIMES THEY COME BACK, (8/31/1990) (Box >204)
  Writers: Rosenthal, Mark; Konner, Lawrence
- SON OF THE MORNING STAR, (3/12/1990) (Box >185)
  Writers: Mathison, Melissa; Connell, Evan S.
- SON-RISE, (12/2/1978) (Box >194)
  Writers: Kandel, Stephen; Kaufman, Barry Neil
- SON'S PROMISE, A, (11/7/1989) (Box >172)
  Writers: Stratton, Bill; Inman, Robert
- SPACE, (2/24/1984) (Box > 59)
  Writers: Silliphant, S.
- SPACE (MINISERIES BIBLE), (no date) (Box >139)
- SPACE (PART I), (no date) (Box >139)
  Writers: Silliphant, Stirling
- SPACE (PART I), (9/30/1983) (Box >139)
- SPACE (PART III), (9/10/1983) (Box > 35)
- SPARKLING CYANIDE, (4/5/1983) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Young, Robert Malcom; Grafton, Sue & Humphrey, Steve
- SPARKS, (9/12/1989) (Box > 74)
  Writers: Bensink, John Robert; Svanoe, Bill
- SPARROW, (no date) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Bernstein, Walter; Adams, Richard
- SPECIAL BULLETIN, (12/20/1982) (Box > 85)
  Writers: Herskovitz, M.
- SPECIAL GIFT, A, (6/29/1979) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Crays, Durrell Royce; Simon, Marcia L.
- SPECIAL OLYMPICS WORLD GAMES (1995 Special), (no date) (Box >222)
- SPELL (THE), (11/12/1976) (Box >140)
  Writers: Taggert, Brian
- SPLASH, TOO, (9/9/1987) (Box > 38)
  Writers: Singer, Bruce Franklin
- SPLENDOR IN THE GRASS, (3/16/1981) (Box > 24)
  Writers: Inge, William; Herzfeld, John (adapted by)
- SPOONER, (no date) (Box >210)
  Writers: Baloff, Peter; Wollert, Dave
- SPOT MARKS THE X, (11/13/1985) (Box >184)
  Writers: Jenning, Michael
- SPRAGGUE, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SST-DEATH FLIGHT, (11/23/1976) (Box >156)
  Writers: Roberts, William; Joseph, Robert L.
- STAGECOACH, (no date) (Box > 1)
- STAIRCASE (THE), (7/30/1997) (Box >255)
- STALK THE WILD CHILD, (8/5/1976) (Box >163)
  Writers: Packer, Peter
- STAND (THE), PART I, (7/7/1992) (Box >183)
  Writers: King, Stephen
- STAND (THE), PART II, (7/7/1992) (Box >183)
- STAND (THE), PART III, (7/7/1992) (Box >183)
- STAND (THE), PART IV, (7/7/1992) (Box >183)
- STAND BY YOUR MAN, (11/7/1980) (Box > 88)
- STAR, (3/19/1993) (Box >247)
  Writers: Labine, Claire
- STAR MAKER (THE) (PART I), (1/28/1981) (Box >180)
- STAR MAKER (THE) (PART II), (1/31/1981) (Box >180)
- STAR SEARCH, (no date) (Box >238)
- STAR SPANGLED CELEBRATION (Special), (no date) (Box >239)
- STARFLIGHT ONE, (no date) (Box > 27)
- STARFLIGHT ONE, (3/16/1982) (Box > 27)
- STARFLIGHT: THE PLANE THAT COULDN'T LAND, (5/21/1982) (Box >161)
- STARK, (11/19/1984) (Box > 26)
- STAYING AFLOAT, (3/31/1993) (Box >247)
  Writers: Sadowski, Michael
- STEEET (THE), (6/30/1996) (Box >210)
- STEELTOWN, (12/18/1978) (Box > 61)
- STEPHEN KING'S THE TOMMYKNOCKERS (PART I), (7/28/1992) (Box >160)
  Writers: Cohen, Lawrence D.; King, Stephen
- STEPHEN KING'S THE TOMMYKNOCKERS (PART II), (7/28/1992) (Box >172)
- STILLWATCH, (9/18/1986) (Box > 93)
  Writers: Peckinpah, David E.; Koenig, Laird; Clark, Mary Higgins
- STOMPIN' AT THE SAVOY, (9/16/1991) (Box >123)
  Writers: Sawyer, Beverly M.
- STONE FOX, (no date) (Box > 13)
- STONE PILLOW, (2/28/1985) (Box > 61)
- STOP AT NOTHING, (7/9/1990) (Box >127)
  Writers: Johnson, Stephen W.
- STORMIN' HOME, (6/11/1984) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Booth, James; Jameson, Jerry
- STORMIN' HOME, (9/10/1984) (Box > 16)
- STORMY CITY BOWL, (6/14/1978) (Box > 10)
  Writers: Proctor, J.
- STORYTELLER (THE), (8/3/1977) (Box >132)
- STRANGE CASE OF JEKYLL/HIDE, (no date) (Box > 41)
- STRANGE HOMECOMING, (no date) (Box >158)
- STRANGER IN THE HOUSE, (10/27/1981) (Box > 61)
  Writers: Trevey, K.
- STRANGER WAITS, A, (7/25/1986) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Crays, Durrell Royce
- STRANGERS IN 7A (THE), (8/14/1972) (Box >208)
  Writers: Roth, Eric
- STRANGERS: THE STORY OF A MOTHER AND DAUGHTER, (10/3/1977) (Box >194)
  Writers: Guzman, Michael
- STRAYS, (4/29/1991) (Box >205)
  Writers: Cassidy, Shaun
- STREET OF DREAMS, (no date) (Box > 15)
- STREETS OF L.A. (THE), (6/20/1979) (Box >177)
  Writers: Gluck, Marvin A.
- STRIKE FORCE, (12/3/1974) (Box >147)
  Writers: Hirson, Roger O.; Grosso, Sonny
- STUDS LONIGAN (PARTS I, II, III), (3/27/1978) (Box > 61)
- STUNT SEVEN, (1/2/1979) (Box >190)
  Writers: Shaw, David
- SUDDEN FURY (wrapped), (2/6/1992) (Box >137)
  Writers: Bombeck, Matthew
- SUDDENLY SINGLE, (4/8/1971) (Box >139)
- SUDDENLY, LOVE, (3/27/1978) (Box >153)
- SUMMER FANTASIES, (2/28/1984) (Box >188)
  Writers: Down, Rena
- SUMMER GIRL, (8/2/1982) (Box > 26)
- SUMMER GIRL, (1/5/1982) (Box >206)
  Writers: Carothers, A.J.
- SUMMER MY FATHER GREW UP (THE), (4/2/1990) (Box >125)
  Writers: Jennings, Sandra
- SUMMER SOLSTICE (SPECIAL), (7/26/1980) (Box >244)
  Writers: Phillips, Bill
- SUN ALSO RISES (THE) (PARTS I, II), (12/13/1983) (Box > 10)
- SUNSET LIMOUSINE, (1/21/1982) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Clement, Dick; La Frenais, Ian
- SUNSET LIMOUSINE, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SUNSHINE, (7/12/1973) (Box >202)
- SURROGATE (THE), (5/27/1994) (Box >209)
  Writers: Hartung, Raymond; Bell, Elisa (draft)
- SURVIVAL OF DANA (THE), (1/21/1979) (Box >152)
  Writers: Norwood, Frank E.
- SURVIVING, (7/9/1984) (Box >115)
- SVENGALI, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SWAN SONG, (2/1/1979) (Box > 61)
  Writers: Bloom, J.
- SWEET LORRAINE, (no date) (Box > 10)
- SWITCHED AT BIRTH (PART I & II), (1/7/1991) (Box >216)
  Writers: O'Hara, Michael
- SYBIL, PART I, (4/8/1976) (Box >124)
  Writers: Stern, Stewart
- SYBIL, PART II, (6/22/1976) (Box >124)
- TAGGET, (9/10/1990) (Box >125)
  Writers: Fischer, Peter S.; Heffron, Richard
- TAGGET, (no date) (Box >205)
- TAIL GUNNER JOE, (6/30/1976) (Box >203)
- TAKE YOUR BEST SHOT, (3/19/1982) (Box >114)
- TALE OF TWO CITIES, A, (5/23/1980) (Box >113)
- TALES OF THE BRASS MONKEY, (11/12/1981) (Box > 61)
  Writers: Bellisario,D.P.
- TARANTULAS, (8/10/1977) (Box >196)
  Writers: Trueblood, Guerdon; Groves, John
- TARZAN IN MANHATTAN, (11/23/1988) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Sandor, Anna; Gough, Willian
- TASTE OF EVIL, A, (7/12/1971) (Box > 10)
- TATTERED WEB, A, (no date) (Box >136)
- TELETHON, (8/12/1977) (Box >148)
  Writers: Roberts, William; Ludwig, Jerry
- TELEVISION ACADEMY HALL OF FAME-II (Special), (no date) (Box >227)
- TEN COMMANDMENTS: THOU SHALL NOT KILL, (11/1/1978) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Elder III, Lonne; Rapoport, I.C.
- TENAFLY, (7/24/1972) (Box > 81)
- TENTH MONTH (THE), (9/29/1978) (Box > 60)
- TERROR AMONG US, (no date) (Box > 23)
- TERROR AMONG US, (12/10/1979) (Box >132)
  Writers: Barnes, Dallas; Barnes, JoAnne
- TERROR ON HIGHWAY 91, (4/20/1987) (Box >184)
  Writers: Schoffman, Stuart
- TERROR OUT OF THE SKY, (8/14/1978) (Box >166)
- TERRY FOX STORY (THE), (7/10/1982) (Box >167)
- TEXACO STAR THEATRE...OPENING NIGHT (SPECIAL), (6/7/1982) (Box >251)
- THADDEUS ROSE AND EDDIE, (no date) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Wittliff, William D.
- THAT CERTAIN SUMMER, (11/6/1972) (Box >104)
- THE GIRL MOST LIKELY TO?, (7/18/1973) (Box >257)
  Writers: Rivers, Joan
- THIEF (FORMERLY: A DAY IN THE LIFE OF A BURGLAR), (no date) (Box >101)
  Writers: Black, John D.F.
- THIN ICE, (1/1/1980) (Box > 91)
- THIN ICE, (6/17/1980) (Box > 60)
- THIRD DEGREE BURN, (no date) (Box > 17)
- THIRD GIRL FROM THE LEFT (THE), (no date) (Box >129)
  Writers: Previn, Dory
- THIS GIRL FOR HIRE, (5/24/1983) (Box >187)
  Writers: Fisher, Terry Louise; Brown, Steve
- THIS MAN STANDS ALONE, (6/2/1977) (Box >109)
- THIS WIFE FOR HIRE, (11/21/1984) (Box > 62)
  Writers: Segall, D.
- THORNBIRDS (THE), (5/1/1995) (Box >216)
  Writers: Stevens, David
- THOSE SECRETS, (7/3/1990) (Box >249)
- THOU SHALT NOT KILL, (11/1/1978) (Box >246)
  Writers: Elder, Lonne III; Rapoport, I.C.
- THOU SHALT NOT KILL, (11/1/1978) (Box >164)
- THREE EYES, (3/18/1980) (Box > 62)
  Writers: VanScoyk, R.
- THREE ON A DATE, (11/28/1977) (Box >157)
  Writers: Norell, Michael; Kahn, Bernard
- THREE ON A MATCH, (11/13/1986) (Box > 34)
  Writers: Bessisario, Donald P.
- THREE SOVEREIGNS FOR SARAH (PARTS I, II), (9/1/1982) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Pisano, Victor R.
- THREE WISHES FOR JAMIE, (6/27/1986) (Box >101)
- THREE WISHES OF BILLY GRIER (THE), (5/8/1984) (Box >144)
- THREESOME, (2/9/1984) (Box >210)
  Writers: Marcus, Lawrence B.
- THURSDAY'S CHILD, (2/26/1981) (Box > 11)
- TIME FOR MIRACLES, A, (12/20/1979) (Box >113)
- TIME TO TRIUMPH, A, (9/6/1985) (Box >135)
- TIMEBOMB, (1/19/1984) (Box >173)
  Writers: Claridge, Westbrook
- TIMEPIECE, (10/15/1996) (Box >255)
- TIMESTALKERS, (4/30/1986) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Clemens, Brian; Spooner, Dennis
- TITANIC, (5/7/1996) (Box >207)
  Writers: Camerob, James
- TO ALL MY FRIENDS ON SHORE, (9/27/1971) (Box >111)
  Writers: Sloane, Allan
- TO FIND MY SON, (9/26/1979) (Box > 11)
- TO KILL A COP (PART II), (6/14/1977) (Box >143)
  Writers: Tidyman, Ernest
- TO KILL A COPY (PART I), (7/26/1977) (Box >143)
- TO LIVE FOR (Released as My Last Love), (8/8/1995) (Box >256)
  Writers: Ford, Katie
- TO RACE THE WIND, (5/16/1979) (Box > 97)
- TO RACE THE WIND, (6/19/1979) (Box >140)
- TOMMYKNOCKERS (THE) see STEPHEN KING'S THE TOMMYKNOCKERS, (no date) (Box >)
- TOP OF THE HILL (THE), (2/14/1979) (Box > 96)
  Writers: Bercovici, Eric; Shaw, Irwin (story by)
- TOPPER, (5/30/1979) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Kirgo, George; Kascia, Mary; Scheff, Michael
- TORN BETWEEN TWO LOVERS, (7/24/1978) (Box >190)
  Writers: Silverton, Doris; Lakin, Rita
- TORN BETWEEN TWO LOVERS, (11/9/1978) (Box > 62)
  Writers: Silverton, D.
- TOUGHEST MAN IN THE WORLD (THE), (9/21/1983) (Box > 26)
- TOUGHLOVE, (2/5/1985) (Box > 62)
  Writers: Hall, K.
- TRACKDOWN: FINDING THE GOODBAR KILLER, (6/28/1982) (Box >187)
- TRACKER (THE), (8/14/1987) (Box > 16)
- TRADE OFF (THE), (5/17/1994) (Box >206)
  Writers: Koval, Paul; FitzGerald, Ed
- TRADE WINDS, (11/2/1993) (Box >214)
  Writers: Dixon, Peter L.
- TRAIL OF TEARS, (no date) (Box >216)
  Writers: Gibson, Christel D.; Gibosn, Howard R.
- TRANSPLANT, (no date) (Box >129)
- TRAPPED, (no date) (Box > 9)
- TRAUMA CENTER, (2/17/1981) (Box > 62)
- TRAVELING MAN, (12/4/1988) (Box >101)
  Writers: Taylor, David
- TRAVELING MAN, (11/11/1988) (Box >146)
- TRAVELING MAN, (no date) (Box >146)
- TRAVIS LOGAN D.A., (11/27/1970) (Box >162)
  Writers: Lewis, Andy
- TRAVIS McGEE, (3/29/1982) (Box >203)
- TREE GROWS IN BROOKLYN, A, (12/5/1973) (Box > 90)
- TRIANGLE FACTORY FIRE SCANDAL (THE), (2/1/1978) (Box >164)
  Writers: Brez, Ethel; Brez, Mel
- TRIBES, (5/25/1970) (Box >117)
  Writers: Wynn, Tracy Keenan; Schwartz, Marvin
- TRICK OF THE EYE, (6/6/1994) (Box >241)
- TRICKS OF THE TRADE, (7/22/1988) (Box > 67)
- TRILOGY IN TERROR, (11/15/1974) (Box >193)
- TROUBLE COMES TO TOWN, (6/1/1972) (Box >107)
  Writers: Westheimer, David
- TRUMAN, (2/19/1995) (Box >220)
  Writers: Rickman, Tom; McCullough, David
- TRUMAN CAPOTE'S "THE GLASS HOUSE", (11/7/1971) (Box >136)
  Writers: Wynn, Tracy Keenan; Capote, Truman (story by)
- TURN OF THE SCREW, (no date) (Box > 11)
- TURNING POINT OF JIM MALLOY (THE), (1/10/1975) (Box >184)
  Writers: Gilroy, Frank D.
- TUSKEGEE AIRMEN (THE), (1/30/1995) (Box >220)
  Writers: Hutchinson, Ron; Qualles, Paris
- TWILIGHT MAN (THE), (9/5/1995) (Box >255)
  Writers: Korris, Jim
- TWILIGHT OF THE GODS (THE), (12/20/1995) (Box >217)
  Writers: Tolins, Jonathan; Bass, Seth E.
- TWIN DETECTIVES, (1/29/1976) (Box >165)
  Writers: Specht, Robert; Chambers, Everett
- TWO, (1/31/1995) (Box >214)
  Writers: Craig, Charles Grant
- TWO AND A HALF DADS, (9/30/1985) (Box >185)
  Writers: Farr, Gordon
- TWO FATHERS, (8/23/1984) (Box >194)
  Writers: Kinghorn, David J
- TWO KINDS OF LOVE, (3/23/1983) (Box >167)
  Writers: Nelson, Peter; Mann, Peggy
- TYSON, (4/9/1994) (Box >211)
  Writers: Johnson, Robert P.
- UNCOMMON LOVE, AN, (6/21/1983) (Box >149)
  Writers: Freeman, Seth
- UNCOMMON LOVE, AN, (no date) (Box > 13)
- UNDER SIEGE, (9/5/1980) (Box >205)
  Writers: Woodward, Bob; Williamns, Christian
- UNDERGROUND FATHER: FUGITIVE FROM JUSTICE, (8/29/1995) (Box >255)
- UNHOLY MATRIMONY, (12/16/1987) (Box > 3)
- USERS (THE), (1/20/1978) (Box >110)
  Writers: Shaw, Robert J.
- USERS (THE), (3/10/1978) (Box >115)
- V (PART I), (9/7/1982) (Box > 62)
  Writers: Johnson, K.
- V (PARTS I-II), (12/30/1983) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Buck, Craig; Frolov, Diane; Goldman, Peggy
- V (PARTS III-IV), (1/26/1984) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Taggert, Brian; Frolov, Diane
- V (PARTS V-VI), (12/15/1983) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Buck, Craig; Frolov, Diane
- VALENTINE, (no date) (Box >246)
  Writers: Malloy, Merrit; Philips, Lee
- VALENTINE, (7/12/1979) (Box > 95)
  Writers: Appet, Leah
- VALENTINE'S DAY LOVE BOAT, A, (3/31/1989) (Box >102)
  Writers: Garman, Stephanie; White, Hollace
- VALENTINE'S SECOND CHANCE (SPECIAL), (11/8/1976) (Box >243)
- VALLEY OF THE DOLLS (PART I), (12/19/1980) (Box > 63)
- VALLEY OF THE DOLLS (PART I), (7/21/1980) (Box > 62)
  Writers: Stevens, L.
- VALLEY OF THE DOLLS (PART II), (12/19/1980) (Box > 63)
- VALLEY OF THE DOLLS (PART II), (7/21/1980) (Box > 62)
- VAMPIRE, (10/20/1978) (Box >190)
  Writers: Bochco, Steven; Kozoll, Michael
- VAMPIRE, (2/9/1979) (Box > 60)
  Writers: Bochco, Steven; Kozoli, Michael
- VELVET, (10/26/1983) (Box > 80)
- VELVET (PILOT), (1/30/1984) (Box > 26)
- VENGEANCE: THE STORY OF TONY CIMO, (3/20/1985) (Box > 32)
- VERY SPECIAL DORA HALL (THE) (SPECIAL), (6/28/1970) (Box >244)
- VICTIMS, (3/16/1981) (Box >203)
  Writers: Wood, William; Bomberg, Conrad
- VICTIMS FOR VICTIMS: THE THERESA SALDANA STORY, (1/26/1984) (Box > 60)
  Writers: Heinemann, Arthur
- VICTIMS FOR VICTIMS: THE THERESA SALDANA STORY, (4/4/1984) (Box > 63)
  Writers: Heinemann, A.
- VIRTUAL SEDUCTION, (2/3/1995) (Box >248)
  Writers: Gamble-Risley, Michelle; Widmaier, William
- VISIONS..., (7/18/1972) (Box >119)
- WAIKIKI, (9/28/1979) (Box > 11)
- WAIT TILL YOUR MOTHER GETS HOME, (5/19/1982) (Box > 11)
- WALKERS (PART I, II), (2/27/1989) (Box > 16)
- WALLENBERG (PART I, II), (7/17/1984) (Box >197)
  Writers: Green, Gerald
- WAR OF CHILDREN, A, (no date) (Box >130)
- WAR OF CHILDREN, A, (8/1/1972) (Box >135)
- WASHINGTON MISTRESS, (5/22/1981) (Box >103)
- WATCH COMMANDER (THE), (10/7/1988) (Box > 15)
- WAYS AND MEANS, (no date) (Box 257)
- WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION, (no date) (Box >240)
- WEB OF DECEPTION, (7/19/1993) (Box >204)
  Writers: Screiner, Nevin
- WEDLOCK, (10/1/1990) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Miller, Broderick
- WEEKEND WAR, (9/23/1987) (Box > 33)
  Writers: WIDEN, GREGORY
- WELCOME HOME, JOHNNY BRISTOL, (1/12/1971) (Box >111)
  Writers: Greenberg, Stanley R.
- WEST SIDE WALTZ (THE), (no date) (Box >215)
  Writers: Thompson, Ernest
- WET GOLD, (7/4/1984) (Box >190)
  Writers: Sherwin, Daivd; Eliason, Joyce
- WET GOLD, (3/28/1984) (Box > 3)
  Writers: Sherwin, David
- WHALE FOR THE KILLING, (no date) (Box > 11)
- WHARF RAT (THE), (7/4/1994) (Box >245)
  Writers: Kimatian, Paul; Huston, Jimmy
- WHAT ARE BEST FRIENDS FOR?, (no date) (Box >111)
  Writers: Carson, Rubin
- WHAT'S ALAN WATCHING, (2/29/1988) (Box >244)
  Writers: Blaustein, Barry W.
- WHEELS, (2/27/1982) (Box > 9)
- WHEELS (PART IV), (9/13/1977) (Box > 63)
  Writers: Hamilton, R.
- WHEELS (PARTS I, II, III, IV), (9/19/1977) (Box > 63)
  Writers: Lampell, M.
- WHEN EVERY DAY WAS THE FOURTH OF JULY, (4/27/1977) (Box >152)
- WHEN HELL WAS IN SESSION, (6/19/1979) (Box > 97)
- WHEN LOVE KILLS: THE SEDUCTION OF JOHN HEARN, PART II, (11/11/1992) (Box >184)
  Writers: Goodell, Gregory
- WHEN SHE SAYS NO, (8/12/1983) (Box >158)
- WHEN SHE WAS BAD..., (4/26/1979) (Box >174)
- WHEN THE BOUGH BREAKS, (6/30/1986) (Box >175)
  Writers: Penningroth, Phil; Kellerman, Jonathon
- WHEN THE WHISTLE BLOWS, (11/2/1979) (Box >198)
  Writers: Gordon, Chuck; Kartozian, Tom
- WHEN WE WERE YOUNG, (1/30/1989) (Box >146)
  Writers: Shapiro, Richard; Shapiro, Esther
- WHEN YOUR LOVER LEAVES, (1/25/1983) (Box >157)
  Writers: Leeson, Michael; Trott, Susan
- WHERE ARE MY CHILDREN?, (3/8/1994) (Box >245)
- WHERE HAVE ALL THE PEOPLE GONE?, (6/17/1974) (Box >108)
- WHERE THE HELL'S THAT GOLD!?!?, (no date) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Kennedy, Burt
- WHERE THE LADIES GO, (1/9/1980) (Box >201)
- WHITE LIE, (11/1/1987) (Box >137)
  Writers: Heller, Lukas
- WHITE MAMA, (9/18/1979) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Downs, Robert C. S.
- WHITE WATER REBELS, (5/2/1982) (Box >114)
  Writers: Kouf, Jim
- WHO GETS THE FRIENDS?, (3/20/1987) (Box >145)
  Writers: Garrett, Lila; Krinski, Sandy
- WHO IS JULIA?, (5/19/1986) (Box >174)
  Writers: Sadwith, James S.; Harris, Barbara S.
- WHO IS THE BLACK DAHLIA?, (10/11/1974) (Box >161)
- WHO IS THE BLACK DAHLIA?, (12/11/1974) (Box >159)
- WHO WILL LOVE MY CHILDREN?, (5/28/1982) (Box > 64)
  Writers: Bortman, M.
- WHO WILL LOVE MY CHILDREN?, (10/21/1982) (Box >192)
- WHO WILL LOVE MY CHILDREN?, (6/15/1982) (Box > 64)
- WHY ME?, (8/1/1983) (Box >141)
- WILD AND THE FREE (THE), (5/6/1980) (Box >153)
- WILD AND WOOLEY, (10/26/1977) (Box > 92)
- WILD WOMEN OF CHASTITY GULCH (THE), (5/28/1982) (Box >147)
- WILL THERE REALLY BE A MORNING?, (11/25/1981) (Box > 64)
  Writers: Young, D.
- WILLA, (7/24/1978) (Box >166)
- WILLA, (no date) (Box > 83)
- WILLING TO KILL: THE TEXAS CHEERLEADER STORY, (7/10/1992) (Box >160)
- WILMA RUDOLF STORY (THE), (no date) (Box > 11)
- WINCHESTER '73, (7/18/1966) (Box > 3)
  Writers: Adams, Richard; Kandel, Stephen
- WINDRUNNER, (12/16/1992) (Box >214)
  Writers: DAvis, Mitch
- WINDS OF WAR, (6/22/1979) (Box > 64)
  Writers: Wouk, H.
- WINDS OF WAR (RESEARCH INFORMATION), (12/14/1979) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART I), (6/24/1980) (Box >12)
  Writers: Wouk, Herman
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART I), (9/15/1980) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART II), (9/15/1980) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART II), (1/2/1979) (Box >12)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART III), (2/4/1980) (Box >12)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART III), (9/15/1980) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART IV), (9/15/1980) (Box >178)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART IV), (3/4/1980) (Box >12)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART V), (3/11/1980) (Box >12)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART V), (9/15/1980) (Box >178)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART VI), (5/2/1980) (Box >12)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART VI), (9/15/1980) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART VII), (9/15/1980) (Box >177)
- WINDS OF WAR (THE) (PART VII), (7/3/1980) (Box >12)
- WINTER KILL, (10/29/1973) (Box >110)
- WISEGUY: LIFE IN A MAFIA FAMILY, (2/9/1987) (Box > 29)
  Writers: PILEGGI, NICK
- WITCH HUNT, (2/23/1994) (Box >241)
- WITHIN THE ROCK, (9/8/1995) (Box >255)
  Writers: Tunnicliffe, Gary J.
- WITHOUT WARNING: THE JAMES BRADY STORY, (5/12/1990) (Box >172)
  Writers: Bolt, Robert
- WITNESS TO THE EXECUTION, (12/15/1992) (Box >201)
  Writers: Baum, Thomas
- WOMAN CALLED "MOSES", A, (no date) (Box > 64)
  Writers: Haynes
- WOMAN CALLED GOLDA, A (PART I), (4/10/1981) (Box > 64)
- WOMAN CALLED GOLDA, A (PART I), (7/6/1981) (Box > 64)
- WOMAN CALLED GOLDA, A (PART II), (4/10/1981) (Box > 64)
- WOMAN HUNTER (THE), (7/10/1972) (Box >178)
  Writers: Clemens, Brian; Williamson, Tony
- WOMAN OF THE YEAR, (1/3/1975) (Box > 77)
- WOMAN OF THE YEAR, (10/14/1974) (Box > 77)
- WOMEN IN CHAINS, (9/24/1971) (Box >118)
- WOMEN OF BREWSTER PLACE (THE), (2/5/1988) (Box > 21)
- WOMEN OF VALOR, (1/1/1986) (Box > 33)
  Writers: MCCORD, JONAS
- WOMEN ON SAN QUENTIN, (5/19/1983) (Box >152)
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #3), (4/27/1978) (Box >155)
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #4), (4/14/1978) (Box >155)
  Writers: Schweitzer, S.S.
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #5), (4/14/1978) (Box >155)
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #6), (4/14/1978) (Box >155)
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #7), (4/7/1978) (Box >155)
  Writers: Fielder, Richard; Joseph, Robert L.
- WORD (THE) (HOUR #8), (4/19/1978) (Box >155)
  Writers: Berg, Dick; Joseph, Robert L.
- WORD (THE) (HOURS #1 & 2), (4/19/1978) (Box >155)
  Writers: Berg, Dick
- WORD OF MOUTH, (8/1/1990) (Box > 90)
- WORLD VISION FAMILY SPECIAL, (no date) (Box >230)
- WORLD WAR II: WHEN THE LIONS ROARED, (10/13/1993) (Box >211)
- WORLD WAR III, (3/31/1981) (Box > 78)
- YOUNG LOVE, FIRST LOVE, (5/1/1979) (Box >175)
  Writers: Polier Jr., Dan
- YOUNG PIONEERS, (11/11/1975) (Box >171)
  Writers: Hanalis, Blanche; Lane, Rose Wilder
- YOUNG PIONEERS' CHRISTMAS, (7/26/1976) (Box >163)
- YOUR MONEY OR YOUR WIFE, (8/8/1972) (Box >179)
  Writers: Miller, JP; Craig, John
- YOUR MOTHER WEARS COMBAT BOOTS, (12/13/1988) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Kelly, April
- ZIEGFIELD, (7/22/1977) (Box > 84)